ps3trophies.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy - PS3Trophies

PS3Trophies.com is an online service that allows allows its members to set up personal profiles. PS3Trophies.com members can view each others' profiles, upload and display images, author forum postings, and comment on other users' posts. 

PS3Trophies.com does not sell personal information about its members to any third party, including but not limited to e-mail addresses and names. 

PS3Trophies.com will not share any individual personal information with third parties except as required by law. 

PS3Trophies.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to verify users and to provide basic information to other users. Members may provide additional information at their discretion such as media interests and personal biographies. Additional information is not required for membership to PS3Trophies.com. Any personal information entered into a PS3Trophies.com profile aside from e-mail address and password should be considered viewable by the general public. This information may be used by third parties outside of PS3Trophies.com's control. 

PS3Trophies.com logs IP addresses of visiting users for statistical purposes and to maintain the integrity of our online gaming features and forums. IP's are not shared with any third party. 

From time to time, PS3Trophies.com may provide demographic and statistical information to prospective partners for the purposes of securing advertising and/or for general promotion of the website. This disclosure will not share any personal information of individual users but is intended to give a broad overview of PS3Trophies.com's membership. 

PS3Trophies.com uses cookies to store login information and to record settings to a user's local computer. This stored data does not attempt to "mine" any other information from a user's system or to collect information on sites outside the PS3Trophies.com family of websites. 

PS3Trophies.com takes great care to protect its users personal information but cannot unconditionally guarantee the security of its database from outside attack or compromise. 

PS3Trophies.com allows members to post URL's that may take users to other websites. PS3Trophies.com can make no guarantees as to the Privacy Policies of these sites. 

PS3Trophies.com will update this Privacy Policy from time to time and alert users of the changes via the PS3Trophies.com online forum or alert system. It is the responsibility of the user to be aware of the current policy. 

Questions about PS3Trophies.com's privacy should be directed to us through the Contact Us page.
